Wash away my troubles
wash away my pain
with the rain of Shambala
wash away my sorrow
wash away my shame
with the rain of Shambala...
你修好它了吗?
You got this thing running yet, buddy?
还没 但我把工具都准备好了
Nah, but I got your tools all set.
我们试下发动这玩意儿 好吗?
See if we can get this thing started, okay?
但我们需要汽化器啊
I thought we needed a new carburetor.
也许不需要 来吧!
Well, maybe we don't.Come on
去坐好  我们来发动它
Slide behind the wheel.We'll fire this up.
怎么了 干吧!
What's the matter? Go ahead.
这样太蠢了 没有新的汽化器 它发动不了的
this is stupid.Without a new carburetor,it's not gonna work.
怀有希望 永远都不是蠢事
Having hope is never stupid.
你要相信好事会发生的
You gotta believe good things will happen, and then they will.
懂我说的吗?
Understand what I'm saying?
在这个世界上 儿子
In this world son
命运在你自己手中!
you gotta make your own luck.
好吗 来
All right?Come on.
那你要怎么修呢?
Well, what do you want to fix today?
我们要把这事先停一下
we're gonna have to put that on hold for a little while cause
因为我要去 Vegas 在那里我有一些事要办
I gotta go to Vegas.You know, I got some work out there.
那我们的公路旅行呢?
W-what about the road trip?
我回来的时候大峡谷还会在那儿的
Well,the grand canyon will still be there when I get back,little dude.
有东西给你
hey,I got something for you.
妈妈说...我...不应该
I'm...not supposed to. Mom says.
留着吧 那只是块巧克力
Live a little, Hugo.It's just a cany bar, okay?
好了 我回来会告诉你的
All right.I'll be back before you know it,all right?
自己保重
All right. Hold down the fort?
你是我的小男孩
You're my man? All right.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
■
翻译：    许愿
校对： 许愿
■
双语字幕：    HUXI       七色九天
后期：     梁良      字幕监制：  梁良
■
"the Others" 摘掉了我的头罩 我们在岛的另一边
so then the others take the bags of our heads,the one like in the other side of the island...
他们把Jack Kate 和 Sawyer带走了
and they take Jack, Kate and Sawyer someplace,
并放我回来警告大家 别去找他们...
and they sent me back to warn everyone to stay away...
我做的...
which I did...
现在每个人都吓坏了
and now everyone's freaked out.
他们的离去  Eko的死
With them gone,and what happened to Eko,
他们都吓坏了...
they're all scared...
我也很害怕
and I'm scared.
而且我...
But then I've...
在这里大部分的时候 我都觉得很害怕...
been scared most of my time here,anyway...
除了和你在一起的时候
except when I'm with you.
我很想念你 Libby
I miss you, Libby.
该死的
Bloody hell.
-伙计 你还好吗?  -不能再好了
-Dude, you okay?  -Peachy.
是吗? 你好像一直闷闷不乐...
Really? 'Cause you've kinda been moping the last...
不要和我说这些了 Hurley
look, it's not worth talking about, Hurley, okay?
伙计 你能告诉我一切
Dude, you can tell me anything.
Desmond...
说我会死的
said I was gonna die.
他说他有幻觉...
He...  he... he told me he has these flashes...
预感什么的...
visions, whatever...
在他的预感里 我会死
and in them, I always die.
这就是你和我说的
So this is the part where you tell me
这很荒唐 不要愚蠢了 他脑子有病
it's ridiculous. Don't be daft. He's a nutter.
我想他也许是对的...
I think he might be right...
而且这都是我的错
and I think it might be my fault.
你的错?
Your fault?
我...受到了某种诅咒
I'm... kind a cursed.
死亡总找上我 伙计
Death finds me, dude.
Vincent?
那是一只手臂吗?
Is that an arm?
Vincent 到这里来 Vincent
Here, Vincent.Come here, Vincent.
我们需要那东西
I think we need to get that.
在恐怖的丛林里追一条含着手臂的狗
Yeah, chase the dog with the skeletal arm into the creepy jungle.
-随你的便吧  -那好吧
-You be my guest.  -Uh, okay.
如果我3小时后还没回来 告诉其他人
If I'm not back in three hours,tell somebody.
Vincent!
Vincent 到这里来!
Vincent, come here!
Vincent!
Vincent
Vincent.
太棒了
awesome.
这是每个人的梦想... 赢取大奖...
it's everyone's fantasy...winning the lottery...
一夜之间成为亿万富翁
untold millions falling into your lap overnight.
你会用这些钱干什么?
What would you do with all that money?
有一个幸运者最近买了一间炸鸡店
Well, one such lucky winner recently bought a chicken shack.
我是Tricia Tanaka  和我在一起的是Hugo Heyes
I'm Tricia Tanaka with Hugo Reyes,
亿万大奖获得者
winner of a record $114 million,
明天将会有一个盛大的开张仪式
outside Mr. Cluck's chicken shack in diamond bar,which will be having its grand reopening tomorrow.
Hugo 每个人都想知道
So, Hugo, I think the question on everyone's mind
你为什么要买下这间快餐厅?
is why did you buy Mr. Cluck's?
因为我喜欢炸鸡
Uh... I like chicken.
这是Hugo 从前的老板  现在的雇员Randy Nations
Um, also with us is, uh,Hugo's former boss and now employee, randy nations.
这是每个雇员的梦想 是吗 Reyes先生?
That's probably every working stiff's fantasy,isn't it, Mr.Reyes?
Hugo 自从你赢了幸运大奖 你还做过什么事?
Um, okay, so, Hugo, tell us what else you've done since you got on your lucky streak.
事实上我也碰到许多倒霉事
Actually, I've kind of had some bad luck, too.
我爷爷Tito 突发心脏病死了
My, uh, grandpa Tito died of a heart attack,
我给我妈买的第一栋房子被烧毁了
and the first house I bought my mom burnt down.
我朋友Johnny 和我女朋友Starla 私奔了...
My friend Johnny ran off with my girlfriend starla...
还有那个从我屋顶 跳楼自杀的人
oh, and this guy jumped off my accountant's roof.
停
Cut.
这该死的是什么?
what the hell was that?
你这是在吹嘘吗 Reyes先生?
It's a puff piece, Mr. Reyes.Do you know what that is?
是啊
Yeah.
抱歉 Tricia Tanaka
Sorry, Tricia Tanaka.
你介意我们进去拍摄吗?
Um, uh, do you mind if we go inside and, uh, shoot some b-roll?
-我不知道...  -当然可以
-Oh, I don't know...  -yeah,yeah,yeah. Of course you can.
他很迷信 你知道 店还没正式开张
Oh, he's just superstitious.You know, the ribbon isn't cut yet.
我们走
okay, let's go.
我讨厌这些 我总是拍到些愚蠢的故事
Ugh! God, I hate this.I always get the stupid stories.
-你肯定这没事吗?  -放松点
-Hey, you sure it's okay?  -Yeah, relax.
煎锅旁有保安吗?
The safety guards are on the fryers?
伙计 煎锅都还没用过?
Dude, those fryers are stone-cold. All right?
明天我们也不准备用它
We don't even start cooking till tomorrow.
你听到了吗?
You hear something?
然后摄像机移动...
and then pan through the...
我们的燕麦饼吃完了
well, we are out of dharma oat bars.
-已经没有了?  -是的
-Already?   -Yep.
你查过奶粉后面吗?
Did you check behind the powdered milk?
麻烦你把那包麦圈递给我好吗？
Will you pass me the box of cereal?
麻烦你...把...麦圈...递给我...好吗？
Will you... pass me... the cereal?
从现在开始我要和你说英语
from now on, I will only speak to you in english.
这样你就可以学习英语
It's how you will learn.
一开始会很难...
it will be hard at first...
大伙儿!
everyone, hey!
怎么了 Hurley?
Hurley, what is it?
是"the Others"吗?
is it the others?
-你还好吗?  -发生什么事了?
-Are you okay?  -what's going on, man?
汽车
Car.
我找到了一辆汽车...
I found a car...
翻倒在丛林里
tipped over in the jungle.
你找到了... 一辆车
You found A...  car.
我们能修好它 让它跑起来
And we can totally fix it and get it going again.
就在不远 来吧
It's not far. Come on.
我们为什么要发动那车?
Why do we need to start a car?
因为那会很有趣
Because it'll be fun.
我们要找些乐子
Oh. We could all use some fun.
经过所有这些 我们需要它
I mean, after everything that's happened, we need it.
特别是你 兄弟
Especially you, dude.
谁和我一起来?
So who's with me?
我...要去弄些香焦 抱歉
Well, I... gotta get some bananas. Sorry.
我不这么认为 Hurley
I don't think so, Hurley.sorry, Hurley.
拜托? 你们可以驾驶的!
Come on! Anyone?We're gonna drive it!
谁来啊?
Who's coming?
谢谢你 伙计
Thanks, dude.
你根本就不知道 要去做什么 是吗?
you have no idea what you volunteered for, do you?
来吧
Come on.
我们到了吗?
are we there yet?
如果我没记错的话
If we are where I think we are,
我们的营地就在这片树林的外面
then our beach should be just through those trees.
5分钟就能回到家了
We'll be home in about five minutes.
克制下情绪 小妞
Try to contain your excitement, freckles.
我对为什么只有我们两个人回来并不感到兴奋
Forgive me if I'm not excited about explaining why there's only two of us coming back, James.
也许他们应该解释为什么 没来找我们
Well, maybe they should explain why they ain't come looking for us.
事实上 如果 Locke...
In fact, I'd be surprised if loc... ow!
-怎么了?  -踩到什么了 该死!
-What happened?  -Stepped on something. Son of a bitch!
让我看看 看上去像... 一枚飞镖
Looks like A...  dart.
飞镖怎么会在这里?
How the hell did it get out here?
放松你的脚 好吗?
All right, just relax your foot for a second, okay?
数到3 我就把它拔出来
I'm gonna pull it out. on the count of three. You ready?
1...
One...
我以为你要数到3
I thought you said three.
我想我原谅你了
Yeah, well, anticipation's the worst part.I thought I would spare you.
你要做的就是向我道歉
You know, all you have to do is say sorry.
我们可以重新开始 和往事说再见
We could start again, give each other a clean slate.
往事... 就像"little house"?
Slate...  like on "little house"?
-什么?  -"Little house on the prairie"?
-What?  -"Little house on the prairie"?
Laura Ingalls 在学校黑板上写的?
Laura Ingalls used to write on this little chalkboard at school?
你叫它 "Little house"?
You call it "little house"?
小时候我生了重病 缺了两个月的课
I had mono when I was a kid.I missed two months of school.
我的房车里只能看一个频道
We only got one channel in my trailer.
我们在说什么?
What are we even talking about?
我们什么也没说
Ah, we ain't talking about nothing.
-James...  -我也没什么好道歉的
-James...  -and I ain't got nothing to be sorry for.
那就这样了?
So that's how it's gonna be?
欢迎回家 Sawyer
Welcome home, Sawyer.
欢迎回家 Kate
welcome home, Kate.
Hugo
是你吗 Hugo?
is that you, Hugo?
我的天!
Oh, my god.
发生什么事了?
What happened?
-Tricia Tanaka 死了  -什么?
-Tricia Tanaka's dead.  -What?
Cluck 炸鸡店被... 流星撞毁了...
Mr. Cluck's... it got hit by a meteor...
或是小行星...
or an asteroid...
我不知道有什么区别 但一切都没了
I don't know the difference, but it's gone.
- 这太荒唐了  - 一点都不荒唐
- That's crazy.  - It's not crazy.
是那笔钱
It's the lottery money.
那些数字...我被诅咒了 Tricia Tanaka 也死了
The numbers... I'm cursed.And now Tricia Tanaka's dead
和他的摄影师 都是我的错
and her camera dude, and it's all my fault.
-这是场意外  -这不是意外
-It was an accident.  -It's not an accident.
这是诅咒  唯一停止它的办法...
It is a curse.There's only one way to stop it.
-我要去澳大利亚  -澳大利亚吗?
-I have to go to Australia.  -Again with Australia?
那串数字就是从那里来的
That's where the numbers came from.
精神病院的Lenny...
Lenny in the institution...
他告诉我的
he told me.
Hugo Hugo 等等
Hugo, Hugo, wait.
我可以证明那不是诅咒
I can prove to you you're not cursed.
-是吗?  -是的
-You can?  -Yes.
跟我来 我要给你看样东西
Come here with me.I-I have to show you something.
Hugo!
17年了 你爸爸终于回来了
After 17 years, your father has returned.
你妈不再和你说那些巧克力了吗?
Your mom wasn't kidding about those candy bars.
开玩笑啦
just kidding.
可怜的...
Poor...
Roger
对你的手臂我很抱歉
Sorry about your arm, dude.
Hurley!
里面
In. In.Totally.
我们看看
Let's check it out.
伙计 Roger的啤酒可不少啊
Dude, Roger was on a beer run.
我听不懂你说什么 你要干什么?
oh, man, I suck at charades.You want to what?
你要把Roger 弄出来...
oh, you wanna take Roger out...
然后把车翻过来!
then and turn it over?
我明白了!
Cool. I understand!
数到3
Okay, on three.
1...
One...
2...
two...
一会儿再处理那个
we'll get that later.
什么时候会发生?
So when's it gonna happen?
你在说什么?
When's what gonna happen?
别耍我了...兄弟
Don't play stupid with me..brother.
我当时醉了 如果我说了什么...
I was drunk.You know, if I said anything...
我有权知道我什么时候会死
I have a right to know when I'm gonna die.
-那不是这样的  -那是怎么样的?
-It doesn't work like that.  -What doesn't work like that?
Oliver Twist
Hey, Oliver Twist.
我的东西哪儿去了?
Where the hell's my stuff?
-什么东西?  -你当然知道是什么
-What stuff?  -Oh, you know good and damn well what stuff.
书 色情杂志 还有一瓶酒
I had books, food, porno, a bottle of scotch.
对那瓶酒我很抱歉 兄弟
Aye, apologies for the scotch, mate.
你喝光了?!
You drank it?!
严格来说一共有...3个人
Well, to be fair, there was,uh...there was three of us.
是啊
Yeah, there was.
你 Munchkin 还有谁?
You, the munchkin and who else?
我明白了
oh, I got it.
我们要把他撬起来
We're gonna tip it up.
用手来
Crafty.
Crafty?
对 就像...
Yeah, crafty.It's like...
手工
when you're good at... crafts.
别在意
Never mind.
我的东西在哪里?
Hey, where the hell's my stuff?
-你们在干什么?  -伙计 你还活着!
-What are y'all doing?  -Dude! You're alive!
-还活着!  -是啊 大块头
-Alive!  -yeah, yeah, snuffy.
很高兴又见到你
It's good to see you, too.
你们给自己找了一辆车
I'll be damn. Y'all found yourselves a hippie car.
很酷不是吗?
Pretty cool, huh?
-Sawyer  -Jin-bo
-最近如何?  -很高兴... 见到你
-how you doing?  -Good... see you.
有人最近在学习嘛!
Well, look at that.Somebody's hooked on phonics.
Jack和Kate 怎么样了?
What about Jack and Kate?
他们和你在一起? 他们还好吗?
They with you? They all right?
Kate 和我在一起...
Kate's with me...
但 Jack...
but the Doc...
他还在那儿
they still got him.
没关系
Okay, it's okay.
Jack 会好的 我们都会好的
Jack's gonna be all right. We all are.
真是松了口气啊
Well, what a relief.
一切都在好起来
Nah, see, things are getting better.
汽车 你平安归来... 这都是预兆
The car, you coming back safely...it's a sign.
是啊 预兆就是 我想要回我的东西
Yeah, a sign I want my stuff back.
你要帮我们把它修好
You're gonna help us fix this thing.
我为什么要这样做?
And why in the hell would I do that?
因为里面有啤酒
'Cause there's beer.
他为什么说 "不要回来"?
Why did he say, "don't come back"?
他牺牲自己让我们逃走
He sacrificed himself so we could escape.
他全豁出去了
Probably didn't want it to be for nothing.
Hurley 告诉我们他们放了 Michael 和 Walt
Hurley told us they released Michael and walt.
是的 他们给 Michael 一艘船
Yep. They gave Michael a boat.
他们就一去不复返了
They took off and never looked back.
你看见有其它船吗?
Did you see any other boats?
没有 但他们不会放弃自己唯一的船
No, but something tells me they didn't give away their only one.
-他们可以离开这座岛吗?  -我不知道 John
-So they can leave the island?  -I don't know, John.
那个关你们的地方...他们住那里吗?
This "zoo" where they held you...is that where they live?
我们和他们的一个人一起逃跑...那个孩子叫Karl
We escaped with one of them...a kid named Karl.
他说他们住在这座岛上
He said that they live on this island.
他能带我们去那儿 但 Sawyer 放了他
He could've taken us there,but Sawyer let him go.
为什么?
Why?
那你就要自己去问 Sawyer 了
You're gonna have to ask Sawyer.
-Kate 你去哪儿?  -我不在乎Jack说什么
-Kate, where are you going?  -I don't care what Jack said.
我们必须把他找回来 我欠他的...
They've got him, and we have to get him back.I owe him that...
我要去找人帮忙
so I'm going to get help.
找谁?
Help from who?
那真是个精品啊
Now that's a hell of a Jesus.
Hugo 是个好儿子
Yes. Hugo is such a good son.
他知道我们的爱 来自耶稣基督
He knows of my love for the savior,
所以他委托 Taxco 的艺术家为我雕刻这尊纯金的雕像
so he commissioned artisans in taxco to custom carve for me this statue in solid gold.
这闻起来像意大利面
Wow, that smells like great lasagna.
这是 Trons 一家自制的
The Trons made it themselves.
Hugo在Bennigan 找到他们的
Hugo found them in Bennigan'S.
现在他们是我们的管家
Now they are our butlers.
有什么不对吗 Hugo?
Something wrong, Hugo?
你父亲问你问题呢 Hugo
Your father asked you a question, Hugo.
我父亲?
My father?
好像他从来都没离开过
You're acting like he never left us,
都17年了
like he hasn't been gone for 17 years.
他就这么突然出现了?
And all of a sudden he shows up?
你难道就没有怀疑吗?
Aren't you at least a little suspicious?
我来是因为你母亲打电话 和我说你遇到了麻烦
I showed up because your mom called and said you were in trouble.
什么?!
What?!
那些数字和诅咒
All these numbers and curs.
Hugo 我已经无能为力了
Hugo, I don't know what to do anymore.
你需要你父亲的影响
I thought you needed a manly influence,
他能帮你摆脱这一切
a father to get you to stop this nonsense.
我没有疯!
I'm not crazy!
他回来的唯一原因就是为了钱
And the only reason he's back is 'cause he wants the money.
这可真伤我的心
Oh, now that hurts.
那么好! 谁都拿不到钱!
Well, guess what?There isn't gonna be any money.
Tron 先生 Tron 女士
Ha! Mr. Tron, lady Tron.
我们不需要你们的服务了
Your services will no longer be needed.
这是解雇费
Severance.
相信我 我是在帮你们
Trust me, I'm doing you a huge favor.
你们受到诅咒也只是时间问题
It's only a matter of time before the curse gets you,
然后你们...死或许更惨
and you...  die, or worse.
Hugo 你在干嘛?
Hugo, what are you doing?
摆脱一切...
Getting rid of it, all of it...
钱 房子和家畜...
the money,the houses, the livestock...
而且我要从他开始
and I'm starting with him.
不 Hugo 你父亲要待下来
No, Hugo.Your father is staying with us.
和我们一起住?
Staying with us? Where?
已经17年了 Hugo
It's been 17 years, Hugo.
什么17年了?
What's been 17 years?
我也是有需求的
I have needs.
不不不! 这都不是真的!
No, no, no!This can't be happening!
他必须要走! 我要他离开!
He has to go! He has to!I want him gone!
-不 你不想  -是的 他要走
-No, you don't.  -Yeah, I do.
你为什么不给你父亲看 你车库里的东西呢 Hugo?
Why don't you show your father what you have in the garage, Hugo?
我真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
你一直留着它
You saved it.
you saved it.
我先 滚开
me first now. Come on.
这些回收物都怎么了?
What's up with all this recycling?
我也不知道 伙计
you got me, dude.
看来那些达摩疯子在建什么路
Looks like those dharma freaks were building some sort of dirt road.
这才是我说的
Whoo! Ha ha! Now we're talkin'.
Hugo...
对我来说很好
looks good to me.
引擎没坏 是吗?
Engine's fine, right?
该死...这里怎么有个人头?
Son of...what's a head doing back here?
那是 Roger
Oh, that's just Roger.
我要把它发动了!
I'm gonna start the car now!
即使你在说英语
dude, even if you were speaking english
我还是一个字都听不懂
I wouldn't understand a word you're saying.
放松 这能行的
Just relax. We're good. This'll work.
我有希望
I have hope.
这能行的
This will work.
该死的
damn it.
这又臭又跑了气
It's flat, and it stinks.
你能修好吗? 你知道哪里坏了?
Can you get it to work?Do you know what's wrong?
冷静点 让他专心干活
Chill out. Let the man do his thing.
那啤酒自从 "Rocky III" 就一直放在那儿了
Dude, that beer's been sitting there since before "Rocky III"
也许是"II" 那东西都有毒了
maybe even "ii". It's probably poison by now.
这具骷髅似乎很喜欢
Skeletor seems to like it.
干杯
Bottoms up.
这不好笑 伙计
That's not cool, dude.
他也有妈妈 家庭和朋友
That guy had a mom, a family and friends.
还有名字 不是骷髅... 他叫 Roger Workman
Oh, and a name.Not skeletor... it's Roger Workman.
是工人 你个白痴 这是他的工作
It's work man, you blockhead.That's his job.
他是达摩组织的看守
He was a dharma janitor.
那你也要尊重死者
Yeah, well you should still respect the dead.
你能修好吗?
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.Can you fix it?
不 修不好了
No. No fix.
但你必须得修好
but you have to.
你就不能试一下吗? 我们要让它跑起来
I mean, can't you try, dude?I mean, we gotta get this running.
你别说了 他是对的 他说了"修不好的"
Hey, leave the man alone.He's right. "No fix".
看看这 它根本跑不起来
" Take a look at that mess.There's no way it's gonna get running.
-你多傻啊?  -你有问题吗 伙计?
-How thick are you?  -What's your problem, man?
你为什么不希望它能跑起来?
Why--why don't you want this to work?
我才不关心 他对你这么重要?
I don't care if it works.Why is it so important to you?
因为我们都要有点希望
Because we could all use a little hope.
如果你在寻求希望的话 Ese
If it's hope you're looking for
我们在另一个岛上...
you're on the wrong damn island.
所以这里根本没什么希望
'cause there sure as hell ain't no hope here.
Hugo 该起床了
Come on, Hugo, time to get up.
快啊 大天亮了 我们走
Come on! Rise and shine. Hit the deck.Come on, we're burning daylight. Let's go.
-这耳机是干什么的? -为了防止噪音
-what's with the earphones?  -It's for the noise.
你妈是个很有激情的女人
Oh, well, your mother's a very passionate woman.
真是恶心
That is disgusting.
来 我们要去冒险
Come on. We're going on an adventure. Let's go.
我不去任何地方
I'm not going anywhere with you.
就这一件事 我和你
look, just do this one thing with me.
如果这不行的话 那你就去澳大利亚 我不会阻止你的
If it doesn't work,you can go to Australia.I won't stop you. Okay?
去干什么?
What one thing?
我们要打破诅咒
We're gonna break the curse.
-这太愚蠢了  -就给她一次机会吧
-This is stupid.  -Just give her a chance, man.
请切牌
Cut the deck, please.
你最近发了一笔大财
You've recently come into a great deal of money.
新闻里到处都是
Could've seen that on the news.
但带来的不是幸福
But it hasn't brought you happiness.
带来的是不幸
No, it's brought you great misfortune.
这个新闻里可没有
She didn't see that on the news.
我看见了一串数字
I'm seeing numbers.
什么数字?
What numbers?
4  8  15  16  23  42
黑暗笼罩着这些数字...
There's darkness around these numbers...
巨大的悲剧
great tragedy.
我...很抱歉
I'm... I'm sorry.
什么? 是什么?
What? What is it?
死亡...
Death...
徘徊在你身边...
surrounds you...
还将会越来越多
and more is coming.
请把你的手给我
Your hands, please.
你被诅咒了...
There's a curse on you...
但可以被除掉
but it can be removed.
Hugo 我要你把衣服脱了
Now, Hugo, I need you to remove your clothes.
我的衣服?
My clothes?
那个诅咒在你的体内
A curse is like an unwelcome entity that lives inside you
必须得除掉它
and it must be exorcised.
是我父亲让你这样做的吗?
did my dad put you up to this?
-什么?  -Hugo 拜托
-What?  -Hugo, please.
如果你承认是我爸让你这么说的话这1000块就是你的了
I'll give you $1,000 right now if you admit that my dad told you to say this stuff.
巫术不能遭到亵渎 你怎么敢...
The mystic arts are not subject to bribes.How dare you...
-$10,000.  -是你父亲让我这样说的
-$10,000.  -Your dad put me up to it.
我只是想帮助你
I was just trying to help.
帮谁?
Help who?
啤酒
Beer
说的对
Bingo. Beautiful.
汽车
Car.
不错
Okay
煎饼大叔
ernational house of pancakes.
你在那边干什么?
What are you doing over there?
-我在祷告  -为了什么?
-I'm praying.  -Praying for what?
帮助
Help.
我来帮你吧
Well, hell, I got you  little help right here.
伙计!
Du! Hey, dude.
不要闷闷乐的
Stop moping. Come on.
我没有 我在思考
I'm not moping. I'm thinking.
当人们望着大海一动不动
When people stare out at the cean and get all quiet-like
他们就是在闷闷不乐
they're moping.
起来跟我走
So get up and come with me.
我们找到的车...
That car I found...
我们要发动它
we're getting it running.
要干嘛?
What's the point?
-你这是干嘛?  -把忧愁打掉
-What did you do that for?  -Snap out of it.
不要因为有人说你会死  就折磨自己
Stop feeling sorry for yourself cause someone said you're gonna die.
我有个能帮助我们两个的主意
I got an idea that's gonna help us both.
现在...
Now...
这很危险
it is dangerous
你会死的机会很大
and there's a very good chance that you will die.
这么说是想让我和你一起去吗?
This is supposed to convince me to come with you?
如果你死不了
It is, 'cause if you don't die
我们就赢了
then we win.
赢?
Win?
我不知道你怎么了
Look, I don't know about you,
但最近我一直不走运
but things have really sucked for me lately,
我真的很需要这个胜利
and I could really use a victory.
让我们赢一次吧
So let's get one, dude.
让我们把车子发动起来
Let's get this car started.
当着死神的面和他说 "随便你 伙计"
Let's look death in the face and say, "whatever, man".
让我们掌握自己的命运
Let's make our own luck.
你怎么说?
What do you say?
对不起
I'm sorry.
不错 继续
Okay, nice. Keep it coming.
你...是...对的
you... were... right.
两句了 再来
Okay. That's two. Hit me.
你穿这条裤子不显得很胖
Those pants don't make you look fat.
现在你懂了...女生最爱听的三句话
now you got it... the only three things a woman needs to hear.
起来 我们有活干了
come on, get up. We got work to do.
你有问题吗 傻大个?
What's your problem, Jumbotron?
闭嘴 红...脖子... 的男人
Shut up, red... neck... man.
说的好
Touche.
Jiminy Cricket 在这儿干什么?
What's Jimy Cricket doing here?
-我们需要人手  -来干嘛?
-We need another man.  -Another man for what?
来推这车子 伙计
To push this car, dude.
推? 推到哪里去?
Push it? Push it where?
用力 用力 用力
go, go, go, go.
这会很刺激的
oh, this is gonna be real good.
你去定澳大利亚了?
So you're going to Australia, huh?
为了那串数字跑那么远...
Long way to go 'cause some stupid numbers...
我真的希望你走开
I'd really like you to leave.
当你母亲告诉我彩票的事时
When your mom called me about the lottery,
我差点昏过去
I was on my bike before she could hang the phone up.
我老了
I'm getting old.
要退休了
Yeah, I-I saw my retirement.
你是对的
You're right.
我来是为了钱
I'm here for the money.
你什么也拿不到
Well, you're not getting any of it.
我不是要和你说这个
Well, that's not why I'm here talking to you now.
我来想告诉你 即使你去澳大利亚 诅咒还会继续
I'm here talking to you now because going to Australia's not gonna break any curse
你不必去那里
You don't need to leave.
你...你只需要一点希望
You just... you need a little hope.
我们自己掌握命运 Hugo
We make our own luck, Hugo.
知道你应该怎么做吗?
You know what I think you should do?
什么?
What?
你应该弄走这些钱...
I think you should give away the money...
全部
all of it, every penny.
只需留下足够买...
Just save enough for a...
一个汽化器的钱
a carburetor.
去Camaro工作
Work on the camaro, you know
就你和我
just you and me.
还有我欠你的公路旅游
Take it off the blocks and make that road trip to the grand canyon.
重新开始并不迟
Never too late for a fresh start.
到了悉尼我会寄明信片给你的
I'll send you a postcard from Sydney.
我会等你回来的
Hey... I'll be here when you get back.
你白痴啊? 你不会就这样往下开吧!
Are you nuts?You're not gonna drive down that.
我们要把它发动起来
We're gonna jump-start it.
你们要把它推下去
You guys are gonna push it,and then on the way down,
我会打起离合器
I'm gonna pop the clutch and get it started.
看见那些石头了?
You see those rocks?
如果你不躲开的话会被撞的很惨
All you're gonna do is crash into those real fast,if you don't roll over first.
不行 Hurley
Hurley, no.
伙计们 我知道怎么驾驶
Dudes, I know how to drive.
来吧 我知道能行的
Now come on. Just push me.This will work. I know it.
你来干什么... 来看撞车表演的吧?
And what are you out here for...watch him crash and burn?
我是来"送死"的
I came to ride shotgun.
那就是你们的葬礼了
Well, it's your funeral.
来 让我们实现他们的愿望
Come on. Let's give 'em their ride.
你确定要这么做吗?
Are you sure you want to do this?
胜利或死亡
Victory or death.
推!
Push!
-天啊!  -小心
-whoa! Whoa, jeez!  -Careful now.Here we go.
是时候了 Hurley
Now would be a good time, Hurley.
就是现在!
Like right now!
根本没有诅咒
There is no curse.
命运掌握在我手里
You make your own luck.
根本没有诅咒!
There is no curse!
我靠!真是狗屎运呀!
son of a bitch.
On the road to Shambala
everyone is lucky,
everyone is so kind
on the road to shambala
进来
come in
来吧!
come on
How does your light shine in the halls of Shambala?
Kate 如果你想找到Jack
Kate, if you were looking for help to find Jack
为什么不来找我们?
why didn't you ask us?
两个原因...
Two reasons...
你们不知道去哪里找 你们也没有去救他的动力
you don't know where to look,and you're not motivated.
我不怪你们
And I don't blame you.
你们为什么要  冒着更大的危险穿越丛林
Why would you want to go on another trek across the island,
救回Jack 呢?
risk more lives just to get Jack back?
你错了
You're wrong.
是吗? 那你们为什么不...
Oh, really?Then why didn't you come after...
我们希望他回来 只是不知道去哪里找
not about the motivation,just about knowing where to look.
我们有指南针  我相信如果我们
We got a compass bearing,
找到正确的方位 我们就能找到他
and I'm pretty sure if we follow it,it'll lead us right to him.
怎么找?
How?
太阳直射Eko的棍子 能确切的表示方位
Because of theay the sunlight hit Mr. Eko's stick when John was burying him.
你知道了我们的秘密 那把你的秘密说出来吧?
So now you know our secret.How about you tell us yours?
别开枪!
No! Don't shoot! ...
没事!
It's all right! It's safe!
我们只想谈谈!
We're just here to talk!
你可以出来了!
You can come out!
你们在这里干什么?
What are you doing here?
我来寻求帮助
I came to ask for your help
做什么?
to do what?
我要去"the Others"的营地
I'm heading to the others' camp,
我要找到他们
and if I'm gonna find it,
就要找了解这个岛的人
I need someone who knows the island.
是什么让你觉得我肯帮助你?
What makes you think I have an interest in helping you?
因为他们抓了我 肯定也不会放了我
Because they had me, and they would have never let me go.
如果我没逃出来的话 他们可能要杀了我
They probably would've killed me if I hadn't escaped.
而那个帮我逃跑的女孩...
And the girl who helped me escape...
她大约16岁
she was about 16 years old.
她的名字叫 Alex
And her name was Alex.
我确信她是你的女儿
I'm pretty sure that she's your daughter.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
■